It has begun! That channel! Applause!
What are we going to do today?
Today, I would like to challenge you to dance!
Dancing...
I'm not very good at dancing.
I'm not very good at it.
I think about it sometimes.
I get told that for sure.
Everywhere I go, people say that.
If you're good at that level...
Really.
If it's appropriate.
Today...
We've set a challenge for you.
BE FIRST's Boom Boom Buck
Boom-boom back.
I wonder if it means "Boom-boom-back.
What kind of song is it?
We'll practice it and have them perform it at the end.
How long can you practice for?
About two hours.
Two hours?
As long as we can within the time limit.
But I know you don't know how to take it alone.
That's why we have a guest here today to be your teacher.
Yes, sir.
Please give the invocation.
Today's guest is here.
Good afternoon.
I'm Um...
I'm Takahiro.
I'm Dr. Takahiro Takahiro.
Thank you very much.
I came here to play dodgeball because I like dodgeball.
Then he asked me to play a song by New First today.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I like Sakurazaka, but I wonder if BE FIRST has anything to do with it.
Is there a connection?
We don't even have a connection.
What? I don't want to make a pattern.
I see.
So you've only worked with SKY-HI before.
So why did you invite me?
I don't know either.
I don't know.
Because I like dancing.
I like dancing.
Anno, if you want to dance, you can dance, if you want to play dodgeball, you can dance, if you want to play dodgeball, you can play dodgeball, if you want to play either ball, you can play either ball.
If you want to play dodgeball, you can play dodgeball.
Shall we make a ball?
Let's start with making the ball.
Okay.
Shall we?
Let's start by making a ball.
Which ball shall we start with?
Did you try holding it?
No, this is good.
This... And, it's good if it's cured.
Make it a circle.
I was watching him the other day.
I thought, "He wants to play dodgeball.
Oh, you saw that.
Yes.
You like dodgeball?
I'm not very athletic.
I don't remember playing basketball.
Well, if you played basketball, you'd be great at it.
But my memory is of a pass that hit me in the face.
And my glasses came off and the lens fell off.
It's an unfortunate memory.
This is the ball.
And...
It's okay to get close.
This is the line
At the line.
You don't see a lot of one-on-one dodgeballs.
It doesn't happen very often.
It's a catch-all project, so there's a catch-all bar project.
Let's go one more time.
I'm scared
The dancers move lightly.
Here we go!
Let's go get it!
That's a great move.
We won!
Yay!
That opening isn't quite over yet.
Now let's see this song! Now let's see this song!
Now let's see this song!
Let's see the video of today's dance!
Let's take a look at the video of today's dance!
Up to the beginning of the dance
Fast!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's long.
It's definitely long, the part...
Oh, no, wait a minute.
This is a tough two hours.
This is something you can practice for days, right?
Yes, yes, yes, and you're asking me to do it in two hours... a variety... something that takes days of practice.
And you want me to do it in two hours.
Variety.
Variety, indeed.
I just heard that, so I want to do it while analyzing it.
We're both starting from zero.
I don't want it to be too slow.
I want you to do it at about 30%, and then have him do it faster.
That might work, but it's not the worst I could do.
What's the point of this dance?
As a dance, it looks better when the accentuation and the intensity of the sound is very effective.
Also, the notes are usually 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, which is a grouping of 8.
But you get a good note at the 6 of 1,2,3,4,5,6.
The way to get the right notes in the first place...
I see now that the way to get the notes in the first place
It's very ingenious.
It's very elaborate.
And the movement part...
I think.
For example, the foot throw.
And the angry, angry part.
Not the same steps.
The first one is probably stronger.
The first one is strong, and the second one is niche, and then the third one has a hand.
There's a lot of subtlety in the sound.
What did you think? Watch this song.
I had no idea what you were talking about.
I'm sure what you're saying is true.
But to the untrained eye, the delicate rhythms...
I don't get it.
I guess it's just that it's all in place.
She looks so bold, but she has a very sensitive heart.
Like the beast in Beauty and the Beast.
A beast.
No, it's difficult, it's deep, it's delicate, it's a beast like the Beast in Beauty and the Beast.
No, it's difficult.
Maybe it's too deep.
50% inverted.
You don't have to do this part.
I think we're good here.
Come here.
Gaga, gaga, gaga.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
That's tight.
All right! Here we go.
First.
Bonga turn.
Gah!
Oh, my gosh! It's so sharp!
That's right.
All of a sudden...
Whoa! And then, boom!
Yeah, that's it. That's 80% of it.
I might get tired here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think I'll just leave it at that.
And then it's like...
I'm getting all hot and bothered.
P-p-p-please, please, please, please
I'm gonna get all hot and bothered...
"Goong, goong, goong!
Ha! I thought he was going to go "Par, par, par, par, par, par, par, par, par, par, par, par!
Back!
I don't like that.
What do you think?
Go the other way.
Don't you want to go?
Back!
You're gonna want to go in front.
Like this, like this?
Do it like this.
Goong, goong.
Back, back, back, like this? Poof, grunt, grunt.
Like this.
Ha-ha-ha.
I see.
Can't the teacher do the last dance too?
I can't do this.
I'll take a look at it and see if it's right.
That's it!
Wanya-wanya!
Pow!
Pray, pray, pray!
back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, come on
back, back, back, back, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
kick, kick, kick, kick!
oh my god, my balance is so bad, I'm going to fall down!
guys, this is how it's going to be.
T, T.
That's right, that's right.
Let's keep it a little low, shall we?
Kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick.
Oh, wait, that's too hard.
Kick, kick, kick, kick, kick before thumpyong
Five, six, five, six, go ahead!
Kick, kick, kick, kick, Tong peong before kick
Something's going ping-pong.
Coming through like this.
It's coming.
That's good.
Tong peong
That's right.
This is a difficult thing to do.
Normally, we would have rehearsed a lot.
What would normally take three or four days of rehearsal, they're doing now.
It's an outrageous challenge.
It's a crazy challenge.
It's crazy.
I've never had a dancer teach me.
I'm so happy.
How high can you raise this?
Sixty.
Let's go to 60.
Time?
You think you can do it?
No, me neither.
Uh, de, de, de, de... Yes, yes, yes, yes... Now listen to the phrases.
Two, three, four.
Open.
Gate.
Boom.
One, two, three.
This place is fucked.
What the hell is this?
But listen to the phrase
OK.
Oyas.
Let's see...
One, two, three.
Zupa.
Zoom.
From pointing to
I've got no feet! I've got no feet!
It's hard!
I have no foot here, I have no foot here, I have no foot here
There is no foot
I don't know which standard is right or wrong
Please watch and see!
Kick kick kick kick open the gate
Throw it through your fingers
There is
There is no
Yes.
Which means there's only one missing.
Mostly yes.
Yes.
No. No. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Yes Yes
Yes, yes, yes
I ignore everything.
I'm just copying the moves.
It's not hard to understand.
It's hard to tell.
Come here.
I'll tell you.
It's like a safety check.
Safety check
and then put it back in, like zun zun
Like, zun zun.
Like a jamboree something or other.
It went "zing, zing, zing" in there.
Are you sure you got it right?
It really did fit.
Let me see the sound.
Don, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick.
Point and click, boom, boom, gas boom.
Point and check. Go, zing, zing.
Oh, it's true. It was zinging.
I think I'm getting the general idea. Oh, it was mostly zinging, wasn't it?
I think it might have been more or less right.
Oh, wow.
That's a first, right? First time today?
Yeah, I don't know how you do it.
He's an ogre of an ogre.
I was on the music station the other day.
I was on a music station, and when it was over, I was approached by someone.
He said, "Hey, let's do this project.
I said, "Hey, let's do it!
I ignored him and that was the end.
But it's fun because I like to dance.
Let's go with the sound.
Oh, my God.
Dad, Dad, Dad, you're not going to the Boom-Boom-Ha?
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah.
Zupa zumpa zumpa zumpa zumpa zumpa
Zoom-pa-doom-pa-doom-pa-doom-pa-doom-pa-doom-pa-doom-pa-doom.
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom.
Zoom, zoom, zoom, good, let's pick up the speed.
All right.
Let's go to the world beyond.
Let's go to 80.
Let's take it as far as we can.
Let's go, Boo-Boo! Hah! Hah! Hah! Back in time, back in time, forward in time...
How much time do we have?
Hours and 15 minutes.
Yes, one hour and 15 minutes.
You're all right.
Okay, thank you.
Shall we proceed?
This is such a stoic project.
I'm not usually like this.
Point and check.
Zoom, zoom, zoom.
Padbre
Phrase target
Zung zung zung
Kakapang
So you're free here.
So, shake it out.
Zun zun
Kuka-kaka.
Boom. How does this come out? I can't do it.
왜? 저런게 나와? 못하겠어
디저트
I'm not interested in that.
디저트?
이거 마지막 머리야?
응
I want you to go to the igloo.
기억하고 있어여
음
손가락 손가둥 손가둥 손가둥
파도 부레레 돈
파도 부레돈
파도 부레레?
I think I stepped on the right foot, stepped on the right foot, stepped on the right foot, stepped on the right foot, stepped on the right foot. One more time, ah... I'll keep my hands in the air...
Like a head gouge goucher.
Left Kogara Gurley, right Kogara Gurley
Girly gaggle on the left, girly gaggle on the right...
"Garry in a rut suddenly turned evil...
And then he looks to the side and says, "What's that? And it's like...
There's something going on over here all the time.
I mean, with the inspection and everything...
There's always something.
There's something over here.
Over here.
I wonder what's over here, and what's over there, and what's over there, and what's over there.
And then I went right, and then I went left, and then I went left, and then I went left.
I think I was trying to grab it.
No...
They're trying to grab something that you found.
Yes.
More so... more so... ding, dong, dong, dong...
I'm so confused.
Come to yourself...
It's like...
It's still fast!
It's so hard!
It's still hard
But with this...
It's amazing that you can do it
Here we go.
chest pump
These two are pretty much in the same order
Pong gun
Gung boong
Pong pong
Bom-bom-bom-bom!
Pom-pom
And then back it up a little bit.
Finally, something like "giggle"...
Gugg!
That's good.
That's good, that's good, that's good. When I say "boomer," you throw this like you're throwing a bowling ball.
Boom, boom, boom, yes, and then kick it like a kick.
That channel from the yes.
I don't have time for this.
You're kidding me.
Let's hear the sound.
If it goes 50%, that means it went.
Par-par-par prayer.
Go ahead.
You're not going?
I'm not going.
Angry pumpernickel.
Kick, kick, kick, kick
Kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick!
It's the hardest one, the finger-throwing one.
Pointing point ding dong dong dong dong
Here it is, toot toot
Confusion, confusion, confusion
You've come to your senses?
What is that?
Freedom, freedom, freedom, freedom.
Nyan nyan nyan what is this place? Free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free, free
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong.
98 points
Gentle
From here.
It's from here.
I can't think fast enough.
Oh, man.
It's like you're letting what you've learned seep into your body.
Yes.
When you think before you move.
We lose a little bit of time.
If you do it at a slower speed...
If you do it at a slower speed
But if you actually go faster...
But if you actually go faster
When you transfer the memories from your head to your body
To transfer the memories from the mind to the body.
That's true.
The first time you do it, it's a little bit slower and then you remember.
The moment you think, "Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Suddenly, cat, cat, cat, shake and pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
Cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat, cat...
Some people are like, "Ruff Ruff Ruff!
Cat Cat Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff Ruff
Cat Cat, do something!
Cat Cat Ruff Ruff
Kick, kick, kick
Kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick!
What do you mean, do cat, cat, cat?
I'm doing it like this.
Cat, cat, cat, thump, thump.
Knock-knock, cat-knock.
Knock-knock.
Knock-knock-knock-knock-knock-knock-knock-knock-knock.
That's right! Yes!
Cat cat cat this is a little bit
It's not getting any harder, is it?
It's all right, isn't it? I'm the one who said that.
I'll get you into Tocca 70 or something.
Maybe 80.
80?
Oh, here it comes!
I said 80 all at once.
Just let it go a little bit.
Can you do it?
That's fast.
I can feel it.
Oh, my God.
Relax, Mew.
Oh, you're so desperate, aren't you?
I'm a little too desperate to be quiet.
Oh, this is so hard.
It's so different when it's fast.
Just when I think it's happening...
I'm like, "What's next?
With four times, I can think about what's next, but I can't do that.
I can't do that.
What do you think? Mr. Aoyama, how are you doing so far?
He's doing it so fast.
It's only been an hour or so.
It's tough.
What percentage are you at?
Ninety?
90?
Oh, 90? Yeah.
That's fast.
No, I think it's too fast.
Wait a minute.
It's fast.
Early!
me
Aaah!
I'm such a jerk, but I'm early! I'm early! I'm early!
I'm early!
Quick!
Fast!
Huh?
I'm tired.
I'm very tired.
I don't move this fast in July.
My body's a little jumpy.
You're a little jumpy, aren't you?
Yeah, I know.
I don't know.
I'm sure.
If you suddenly do it for the first time in a while...
It's a disadvantage, right?
It's a disadvantage.
It's not so much that you're going to look cool, it's more that you're going to do this
I might lose money, but I'm going into it, so
Right.
And so it's nice that you're pretty much willing to bite the bullet so far.
Generally, you see, the feeling of impossibility is greater.
It's a little bit....
I'm really trying too hard on the way, and I'm letting my body do the work.
My memory can't keep up.
On autopilot mode?
Yeah. Automatic?
Automatic mode BGM
How's it going? How's it going? How's it going?
BGM
I saw it
BGM.
It's my first time.
I thought it was gonna be like this.
Pow!
You got it?
I got it. I got it. I got it.
You did it.
Did you get it? How'd it go?
It was done.
I'm sure you can do it, Anno-san.
You really do sound like Mr. Takagishi, don't you?
You can do it, right?
In less than two hours.
If Takahiro Sensei teaches me how to do it...
If you do it, you can do it.
That's what I'm saying.
I can go home.
I thought this would last until morning.
Thank you for watching.